Armin Bayat

Turkey



arminbayat@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/armin-bayat-b3804390

Summary

About 4+ years of experience in software and web application design, development and implementation in Financial/Banking systems. Develope and maintain large scale enterprise applications using Java, Spring, and Hibernate. I am interested in learning new concepts and technologies in software engineering fields.

Experience



Software Engineer

Snapp!

Oct 2019 - Present (1 year +)

We are rewriting the financial parts of old projects. In the new project, we use micro-service architecture, We are developing microservices with Java and Go languages. At the same time, we keep old projects that are in PHP.

We are using Java 8 and 11, Spring Cloud Family, Go 1.13, Laravel, Rabbit-MQ, Docker, Open Shift, and Gitlab.



Java Full Stack Developer

Informatics Services Corporation

Jan 2019 - Oct 2019 (10 months)

Development and maintenance of national Cheque Image System (CHAKAVAK) for Central Bank of Iran using EJB, Hibernate and JSF (CHAKAVAK act as an interbank cheque settlement switch)



Java Developer

TOSAN (Banking and Payment Solutions Provider)

Aug 2016 - Jan 2019 (2 years 6 months)

- Development and maintenance of Card Management System (CMS) using Spring and JPA
- Involved in development of EMV card project

Education



hamedan university of technology

Engineer's degree, Computer Hardware Engineering 2011 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications



Java J2SE Developer - آزمایشگاه یادگیری فناوری اطلاعات لایتک - Laitec 2014-9-3615

Laitec - آزمایشگاه یادگیری فناوری اطلاعات لایتک - Java Programmer Beginnner

- Certified Linux Administrator (LPIC-1) Paravid
- Consuming RESTful APIs in PHP with Guzzle LinkedIn
- Microservices: Design Patterns LinkedIn
- Software Architecture: Domain-Driven Design LinkedIn
- Practical Test-Driven Development for Java Programmers LinkedIn
- Learning Java 9 Modularity LinkedIn
- in Java Microservices with GraalVM LinkedIn

Skills

Java • Spring Framework • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Agile Methodologies • Software Design • Test Driven Development • Software Development • Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) • SQL • Databases